<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>HYUNMI OH</title>
    <description>Hyunmi's personal website</description>
    <link>http://localhost:4000/</link>
    <atom:link href="nathanrooy.github.io/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2020 15:03:39 +0900</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2020 15:03:39 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v4.0.0</generator>
      
    
    <item>
        <title>Exploring Design Opportunities for Technology Supported Yoga Practices at Home</title>
        <description>&lt;h3 id=&quot;abstract&quot;&gt;Abstract&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
Yoga is a discipline that integrates mind and bodily exercises practiced for a number of health benefits. Although physical and mental health benefits from practicing yoga are well-known, people address time and cost as the primary barrier to incorporating yoga practices on a regular basis. A cost- effective solution to these limiting factors is adopting at-home practices. However, starting at-home yoga practices is difficult, especially for beginners, due to the lack of feedback on practitioners’ performance. To tackle this challenge, we explore design opportunities for an interactive artifact that can effectively support yoga practices at home that can potentially replace professional personal trainers. Our approach for exploring this design space begins with a user study with a group of yoga practitioners in order to identify design requirements in a yoga practice environment. Based on the results from the user study, we provide some design insights for developing a feedback-based artifact for yoga practice in the home environment. Then, we exemplify how suggested implications can be applied to design with an illustration of a biofeedback-based mat for yoga breathing exercises. Beyond this, we inspect how the mechanism of biofeedback for breathing can be implemented by building a low-cost respiration phase detector to evaluate the quality of breath. The results from the study on the development of phase detector show per-user classifiers can identify respiration phases with mean F-scores of 0.69 for all poses and 0.78 for the baseline pose. This is an acceptable result acknowledging numerous momentary judgments are made to identify each breathing phase. Moreover, per-user classifiers for identifying three yoga poses show promising results, which can expand the application areas of the breathing phase detector. Through this series of context-driven exploratory studies, we demonstrate approaches to investigate design opportunities for technology-supported at- home yoga.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;more-info&quot;&gt;More Info&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;li&gt; &lt;a a=&quot;&quot; href=&quot;http://localhost:4000/Exploring%20Design%20Opportunities%20for%20Technology-Supported%20Yoga%20Practices%20at%20Home.pdf&quot;&gt; Download &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;photo-credit&quot;&gt;Photo Credit&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Photo by kike vega on Unsplash&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
        
        <link>/posts/2020/01/08/yoga-post.html</link>
          
        
            <category>User Study</category>
        
            <category>Speed Dating</category>
        
            <category>Prototyping</category>
        
            <category>Sensing</category>
        
            <category>Machine Learning</category>
        
          
        
            <category>posts</category>
        
          
      </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Detecting Negative Emotions During Social Media Use On Smartphones</title>
        <description>&lt;h3 id=&quot;abstract&quot;&gt;Abstract&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
Emotions are integral to the social media user experience; we express our feelings, react to posted content and communicate with emoji. This may lead to emotional contagion and undesirable behaviors such as cyberbullying and flaming. Nearly real-time negative emotion detection during the use of social media could mitigate these behaviors, but existing techniques rely on corpora of aggregated user-generated data - posted comments or social graph structure. This paper explores how live data extracted from smartphone sensors can predict binary affect, valence and arousal during the typical social media tasks of browsing content and chatting. Results show that momentary emotion can be predicted, using features from screen touches and device motions, with peak F1-scores of 0.86, 0.86, 0.88 for affect, valence and arousal.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;more-info&quot;&gt;More Info&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
This work was led by &lt;a href=&quot;https://mintra-ruensuk.github.io/&quot;&gt;Mintra Ruensuk&lt;/a&gt;, a PhD candidate at UNIST. The outcome of this work has been published to ASIAN-CHI in 2019. Check out details in &lt;a href=&quot;https://mintra-ruensuk.github.io/asian-chi/&quot;&gt;Mintra's portfolio&lt;/a&gt;.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;image-credit&quot;&gt;Image Credit&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
Photo by Erik Lucatero on Unsplash
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
        
        <link>/posts/2020/01/07/emotion-post.html</link>
          
        
            <category>Emotion</category>
        
            <category>Machine Learning</category>
        
            <category>Smartphone Sensor Data</category>
        
            <category>Teamwork</category>
        
          
        
            <category>posts</category>
        
          
      </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Electric Candle</title>
        <description>&lt;h3 id=&quot;abstract&quot;&gt;Abstract&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
Dematerialization in HCI community refers to a process in which contents become disengaged from fixed carriers. In other words, contents no longer require physical medium and can rather flow freely through networks and devices [&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.ijdesign.org/index.php/IJDesign/article/view/1124/554&quot;&gt; Physical Interaction in a Dematerialized World &lt;/a&gt;]. The best exemplar of this phenomenon is CDs being replaced by digital files. 
In this project we focus on dematerialization of physical light sources. Studies on designing interaction methods for dematerialization of light is not new. However, previous studies on light dematerialization either points to emotional aspect of candle usage or introduce usage-specific interactions on screen. In contrast, the primary goal of this project is in enhancing user experience of candle lights using physical interaction design. Th electric candle light introduced in this project is a physical artifact in the form of a candle that can be lit up using finger-swipe motion. We use candle melting metaphor to implement the candle height lowering to the base level as time ticks by for following reason: it helps users to visualize energy consumption.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;system-design&quot;&gt;System Design&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;center&gt;
	&lt;img src=&quot;/images/candle/structure.png&quot; style=&quot;width:50%&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/center&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;technical-implementation&quot;&gt;Technical Implementation&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
* Hardware &lt;br /&gt;
Descending candle frame is implemented with a linear actuator with –driver and configured appropriately to be used with Arduino Nano. Two limit switches have been placed on maximum and minimum location the actuator can reach since the motor can only be driven by a positive or a negative speed. As the motor requires 12V, an external power supply is used. For candle flames, two two-legged LEDs are used. A microphone module is positioned near the 3D-printed flame for receiving blowing input. A pressure sensor along with a button switch is fixed on the bottom part of the candle frame body.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
* Software &lt;br /&gt;
The software program to control all digital and analog inputs as well as output components including button switch, limit switches, pressure sensor, LEDs, microphone, and linear actuator are all coded and managed in Arduino IDE. The code used in this project can be found &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/ohyunmii/candle&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
&lt;center&gt;
&lt;video width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; controls=&quot;&quot;&gt;
  &lt;source src=&quot;/images/candle/candle.mp4&quot; type=&quot;video/mp4&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/video&gt;
&lt;/center&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
        
        <link>/posts/2020/01/06/candle-post.html</link>
          
        
            <category>Interaction Design</category>
        
            <category>HCI</category>
        
            <category>Dematerialization</category>
        
            <category>Tangible Interaction</category>
        
            <category>Prototyping</category>
        
          
        
            <category>posts</category>
        
          
      </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>DINO (Design &amp; Innovation)</title>
        <description>&lt;script src=&quot;//ajax.googleapis.com/ajax/libs/jquery/1.9.1/jquery.min.js&quot;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;

&lt;script&gt;window.jQuery || document.write('&lt;script src=&quot;_/js/libs/jquery-1.9.1.min.js&quot;&gt;&lt;\/script&gt;')&lt;/script&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We started this project for fun. The primary goal of this project was to produce the Solid R4 kart model from scratch. The Solid R4 kart model is the default frame you’re given when you sign up to a popular racing game called &lt;a href=&quot;http://kart.nexon.com/events/2020/0102/Event.aspx&quot;&gt;Kart Rider&lt;/a&gt;. Due to the nature of the project, no specific technical skills were needed to complete this; only a bit of patience. 
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;center&gt;
&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/yz-4brOfaqA&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
This is the video of our club members riding the kart. 
&lt;/center&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;pictures&quot;&gt;Pictures&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;center&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;photoset-grid-custom&quot; data-layout=&quot;213&quot;&gt;
        &lt;img src=&quot;/images/dino/land-5.jpg&quot; /&gt;
        &lt;img src=&quot;/images/dino/land-6.jpg&quot; /&gt;
        &lt;img src=&quot;/images/dino/land-3.jpg&quot; /&gt;
        &lt;img src=&quot;/images/dino/land-1.jpg&quot; /&gt;
        &lt;img src=&quot;/images/dino/land-2.jpg&quot; /&gt;
        &lt;img src=&quot;/images/dino/land-4.jpg&quot; /&gt;
       
    &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/center&gt;

&lt;script src=&quot;/assets/js/jquery.photoset-grid.js&quot;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;

&lt;script type=&quot;text/javascript&quot;&gt;
    $('.photoset-grid-custom').photosetGrid({
    // Set the gutter between columns and rows
    gutter: '5px',
  
    // Wrap the images in links
    highresLinks: true,
  
    // Asign a common rel attribute
    rel: 'print-gallery',

    onInit: function(){},
    
    onComplete: function(){
        // Show the grid after it renders
        $('.photoset-grid-custom').attr('style', '');
    }
});
&lt;/script&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
        
        <link>/posts/2020/01/05/dino-post.html</link>
          
        
            <category>DINO</category>
        
            <category>DIY</category>
        
            <category>KartRider</category>
        
            <category>SolidR4</category>
        
            <category>video</category>
        
          
        
            <category>posts</category>
        
          
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
